(bell rings)
I thought you weren't allowed here.
I'm permitted on school grounds
Oh, I wanted to tell you
I'm available
We need to bring our "A" game
Oh, we're not gonna have any trouble with them.
Not as soon as I have
Shelby Corcoran fired.
(whispers):
She's sleeping with Puck.
Look, that's a really, really dangerous rumor
You're gonna ruin her entire reputation.
That's the plan.
And it's not a lie.
I heard it from Puck.
First of all, Puck is 18, so what he and Shelby are doing,
So all you're doing is you're just,
Sounds like an unfit mother.
And I'll be waiting in the wings
Beth loves her mom.
Shelby is her real mom.
Look, you've done a lot of really bad things, Quinn,
(bell ringing)
Sectionals is in our auditorium for the first time since 1963,
Too much talking, not enough looking
We need to do something upbeat.
Mr. Shue, maybe we need to concentrate
I mean, at least the Cheerios! can dance.
We need star power.
We don't even know where he is.
He's in Kentucky.
It's just across the border from Cincinnati.
It's about a four hours from here.
Even homeless people have Facebook.
Rachel and I might as well get used
There's no way we're getting into NYADA now.
If we don't win at Sectionals,
I pretty much have nothing to live for.
New Directions! is a mess, and we're gonna lose, Kurt,
Every time I open my mouth,
Finn gives me these looks like,
"What does he think he's doing?"
I know what I'm doing.
Hey, guys!
It's so crazy.
I'm sitting
"Wait a second
I know that hair."
What's up, buddy?
Haven't seen you online.
Hi, Kurt.
We've been really busy with Glee Club.
Practicing for Sectionals... together.
Mmm, congrats on the Warbler win at your sectionals.
We're up this week.
Yeah. Well, hey, if there's one guy that can whip New Directions
Right.
I need another coffee.
I don't like you.
Fun.
I don't like you either.
I don't like the way you talk to my boyfriend,
I don't like your smirky little meerkat face,
I don't like your obnoxious CW hair. I'm onto you.
Let's get a few things straight.
Blaine's too good for you.
New Directions! is a joke.
And one of us has a hard luck case
Odds are by the end of the school year, I'll have Blaine
You smell like Craig's List.
What are you guys talking about?
Duh, the next time we're all going out drinking, killer!
Uh-oh.
Well, I gotta run.
But you take care of that
Warbler, Kurt. (clicks tongue)
Wait. This can't be the right place.
Sam works in a bar?
Well, there just aren't a lot of theaters in
Northern Kentucky,
There's a lot of ladies here-- like, older ladies.
Finn, it's no secret that dinner theater appeals
ANNOUNCER (over P.A.):
Good afternoon, ladies!
Are you ready to meet the men of Stallionz?
Then please welcome to the stage-- Cobra!
I didn't know Backdraft was a musical.
ANNOUNCER: Someone get the door,
'cause here comes Mr. Package.
(women screaming)
Oh, God, no.
ANNOUNCER:
And ladies, let's give
♪ ♪
That's not an image I can ever get out of my mind.
Give me a dollar.
What?
Just give me a dollar.
Rach-Rachel...
I tried getting a real job.
DQ was great and I got two free Blizzards a day,
You know how much
I made this afternoon?
60 bucks.
$61... in 15 minutes.
Am I ashamed I work here?
Yeah, I'm ashamed.
My dad got a job working construction to pay the rent,
Your parents don't know that you work here?
No, they just think the DQ pays really well.
I'm good at this.
You're good at it because you have
You're good at it for all
Come back to McKinley, Sam.
We need you for Sectionals.
Tell me you don't want it.
Dude, you're young, you got so much potential.
Working re is, like, throwing your life away.
Okay, I want it... but my dad will never let me.
Don't know till you ask.
Here we go.
Dad, Mom, what
I'm trying to say
They need me to compete at
Sectionals this weekend.
And he could stay at one of our houses,
Not that there isn't
You think you two could go in the other room,
Yeah, totally-- I'm really good at looking busy.
Son...
You had to become a man much sooner
I'm-I'm proud of what we've all done.
It's just that...
I miss being a teenager.
(Mom sniffles)
Hey-hey-hey-hey...
Mom, please don't...
Look, if you cry, I won't go.
I'm just crying because...
(sniffles, sighs)
Though I don't understand why
This gonna make you happy?
You have no idea.
Come on.
Are we sure yet which band members are joining us?
Well, it looks like
"Floppy Hair Bass Dude,"
"Chapped Lips McGee," and "Johnny Tromboner."
God, we're screwed.
No, we're not.
I know for a fact that we're winning.
Hey, great news, everybody.
Sectionals is going to be
Mr. Shue, we all appreciate your endless supply
Not if I can help it.
(all cheer)
Hey.
Hi!
Come here!
I wouldn't be here if it wasn't for Finn and Rachel.
I sort of lost my way, but...
Let's hear it for Sam Evans!
(all cheer)
All right, enough of the sentimental stuff.
It's time y'all get a little country
(all exclaim)
Cheers!
Two, one, two, three.
(Toby Keith's "Red Solo Cup" begins)
♪ Now a red Solo cup is the best receptacle for barbecues ♪
♪ Tailgates, fairs and festivals ♪
♪ And you, sir, do not have a pair of testicles ♪
♪ If you prefer drinking from glass ♪
♪ Hey, a red Solo cup is cheap and disposable ♪
♪ And in 14 years, they are decomposable ♪
♪ And unlike my home, they are not foreclosable ♪
♪ Freddie Mac can kiss my ass! Ooh! ♪
♪ Red Solo cup, uh-huh,
I fill you up ♪
♪ Let's have a party ♪
♪ I love you, red Solo cup ♪
♪ I lift you up, proceed to party ♪
♪ Proceed to party ♪
♪ Now, I seen you in blue and I've seen you in yellow ♪
♪ But only you, Red, will do for this fellow ♪
♪ 'Cause you are the Abbot unto my Costello ♪
♪ And you are the fruit to my loom ♪
♪ Red Solo cup, you're more than just plastic ♪
♪ You're more than amazing, you're more than fantastic ♪
♪ Believe me when I'm not the least bit sarcastic ♪
♪ When I look at you and say... ♪
Red solo cup, you're not just a cup.
God, no!
You're my...
Friend?
You're my friend.
Thank you for being my friend, red Solo cup.
QUINN:
Aw...
♪ Red Solo cup, I fill you up ♪
♪ Let's have a party ♪
♪ Have a party ♪
♪ I love you, red Solo cup ♪
♪ Red Solo ♪
♪ I fill you up ♪
♪ Let's have a party ♪
♪ Let's have a party, yeah-eah! ♪
♪ Solo cup ♪
♪ Do-do ♪
♪ Oh, do-do ♪
♪ Solo cup ♪
♪ Doo-dee-da-ba ♪
♪ Hmm-hmm-mm. ♪
(all cheer)
(plays flourish)
Corn dogs!
I just heard the news that
Trouty Mouth is back in town.
I've been keeping a notebook, just in case
"Welcome back, Lisa Rinna.
"I've missed you so much since your family packed their bags,
"loaded them in your mouth, and skipped town.
"I can't tell you how many times I've wanted
"to enjoy a crisp pickle, but couldn't find anyone
"to suck the lid off the jar.
"I assume you've been working as a baby-polisher,
"where young mothers place their infants' heads in your mouth to
"get back that newborn shine.
"So glad you're back.
"I haven't seen a smile that big
"since a Claymation
Abominable Snowman got
"his teeth pulled by that little gay elf dentist.
Love, Santana."
I missed you, too, Santana.
Oh, my God.
(bell rings)
Hey, Sam, wait up.
I'm sure you've heard
He's got a full scholarship to Ohio State.
Nice to see you, too, Quinn.
No, no, it's a good thing.
See, I'm free, you're free.
And I'm sure that you've noticed that I'm supermodel thin
What do you want, Quinn?
Look, last year
I didn't appreciate you.
But we're perfect together.
Quinn...
I'm gonna get Beth back.
And-And you'd be perfect to help raise her.
You're so good with kids.
What is so funny?
Quinn, you've got
It's a tough world out there, I know.
I've been through it.
You only get one senior year.
Enjoy it.
You know that song "Jack and
Diane" by John Mellencamp?
Please don't sing.
My favorite lyric
"Hold on to 16 as long as you can."
+
Deadlines are this week.
Tina, I already applied to Stanford.
Pre-med.
But you don't want to be a doctor, you want to be a dancer.
Not if it means ripping my family apart.
My dad hasn't said one word to me
West Side Story.
I'll dance in my free time.
Everyone's happy.
Except for you.
Mike, your dad needs to
I miss him, Tina.
I know.
But you have one life, Mike.
One chance to get it right.
Don't be a coward.
Don't call me that.
You won't make it as a dancer
So maybe your dad's right.
Maybe you should be a doctor.
Or maybe he's right, and we shouldn't be together.
(bell ringing)
WILL:
...six, seven, eight.
Bum-bum-bum.
Step and hit.
Come on!
To the beat!
What does it even matter, anyway?
It's not like we have a chance of winning.
Not without the girls.
Sir, girls smell better than ham
Well, that's it then.
We'll take what's most appealing about us as a group,
Yeah, how about, you know, something like, um...
Cute!
I like the spin,
I like the spin.
Try it again.
Yeah.
God, okay, stop, stop.
Look, Blaine,
What we need to sell here is sex.
What the hell is that?
That's a, it's a body roll.
It's not a body roll.
That is sex.
Man's not wrong.
I got light tingles where it's only 50/50 for tingling.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Sam, that's awesome.
That's exactly what we need.
No, that's not, that's not what we need.
We don't have to resort to... that.
It's cheap.
You know, it's selling out.
I came back here to win.
When you're desperate, sometimes you got to,
This is the advantage.
Of course that's what you think; you have to
What the hell does that mean?
It means that
I'm not for sale.
WILL:
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Hey.
Forget it.
(bell ringing)
Is that Sam's face?
Yep. Yours, too.
Don't act so surprised.
After getting bullied so much,
I took up boxing.
I also started the Dalton branch of Fight Club,
What is your problem with me, anyway?!
Ever since I got here, you've given me nothing but crap.
Honestly, dude,
I was kind of jealous.
I felt threatened.
Your talent kind of freaked me out,
I was good enough.
Look, Blaine, I'm sorry.
Uh, I've been acting like a jackass to you.
With Rachel gone, you're the most
And now more than ever, we need to be on the same page.
United.
Tell me what you need me to do.
We have an opportunity.
An opportunity to be remembered at this school
But it all starts right here, with you and me.
I just want to be able to look across that stage at you
No regrets.
Let's get back to work.
(chuckles)
All right.
(bell ringing)
What are you doing?
Holding your hand.
Don't.
Sam, look, I...
I heard about your boyfriend.
Then you heard he's built like a bulldozer.
We had a summer fling.
It was more than that.
I'll always have a special place in my heart for you,
And you need to do the same.
I don't care how big or bad your boyfriend is.
I'm gonna fight to get you back.
+
What's this?
A bootleg of
West Side Story.
Starring your son.
You missed the performance,
Go. Take that with you.
Are you sure?
'Cause if you saw it,
And if you don't make it right, he's going to spend
Tina...
Please.
You want to be a performer, too?
And your parents support this?
They love me.
They love you,
And you children,
Mike to choose, too,
So few opportunities for you.
I know. I've heard the jokes.
I better hope they do
I don't care.
Performing is what I need to do--
And it may be hard,
You know, you're always talking about honor,
Mr. Chang.
Help your son honor his gift.
(warming up):
♪ La, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la ♪
Okay, guys, you're going to want to sing
And if you forget the words, just keep your lips moving.
Hopefully, nobody will notice.
Let's take a few moments to gather our thoughts.
Trouble Tones are on in five.
Good luck out there.
What?
Why would you try and talk to my dad?
You're making things worse.
He almost didn't let me come today.
I'm really disappointed in you, Tina.
Well, that makes two of us,
'cause I'm really disappointed in you.
Hello, Will.
Looking good, ladies!
We just came to say, may the best glee club win.
Yes, and just in case that glee club is us,
I have convinced Miss Corcoran to consider a contingency plan.
SHELBY: Yes, in the event of a New Directions! loss,
Trouble Tones has voted
You're welcome.
Excuse me?
That's incredibly rude, Santana.
We're being nice.
It would be rude if I
I played a note on a tuba.
Thank you for the offer,
Miss Corcoran, but right now,
And we will be winning, Shelby.
We've got it in the bag.
Puck here is going to come through for us.
He's such a shining star, in every conceivable way.
Don't you think?
Good luck, everybody.
See you on the ice.
Sad?
Devastated.
ANNOUNCER:
And now, the judges for this year's
Show Choir Sectional
Come on.
Department of Motor Vehicles
Employee of the Month,
Brandy Englebert!
(cheering)
From the 11th District
Court of Appeals,
Judge Dorothy Saunders!
(cheering)
And Western Ohio's
Birthday Clown of the Year
(cheering)
(horn honks)
And now, let's welcome our first performers.
All the way from Defiance, Ohio, the Unitards!
(applause)
(train whistle blows)
(rhythmic clapping)
("Buenos Aires" playing)
♪ What's new, Buenos Aires? ♪
Oh, my God, it's the Gerber baby.
♪ I'm new, I want to say
I'm just a little stuck on you ♪
♪ You'll be on me, too ♪
Oh, my God, she's good.
Oh, this is torture.
I should be singing that song.
♪ Stand back ♪
♪ You ought to know what you're gonna get in me ♪
♪ Just a little touch of star quality ♪
♪ Fill me up with your heat, with your noise ♪
♪ With your dirt, overdo me ♪
♪ Let me dance to your beat, make it loud, let it hurt ♪
♪ Run it through me ♪
♪ All I want is a whole lot of excess ♪
♪ Tell the singer this is where I'm playing ♪
♪ And... if ever I go too far ♪
♪ It's because of the things you are ♪
♪ Beautiful town ♪
♪ I love you ♪
♪ You're a tramp, you're a treat ♪
♪ You will shine to the death, you are shoddy ♪
♪ But you're flesh, you are meat ♪
♪ You shall have every breath in my body ♪
♪ Put me down for a lifetime of success ♪
♪ Give me credit,
I'll find ways of paying ♪
♪ Stand back, Buenos Aires ♪
♪ Because you ought to know what you're gonna get in me ♪
♪ Just a little touch of, just a little touch of ♪
♪ Just a little touch of star quality. ♪
(cheering)
Wow.
(chuckles)
I didn't count on that one.
Where are you going?
Aren't you supposed to be in the auditorium?
I saw you leave the auditorium.
I know what you're gonna go do.
You're gonna go tell Figgins about Shelby and Puck.
I'm an adult.
I can do whatever I want.
If you want to be a destructive force
Why?
Because we don't want to wreck all the hard work
So we win.
No, not like that.
Look, just... if you're going to go through with this,
It's the adult thing to do.
(sighs)
I got a taste of what it's like to do the wrong thing.
Okay? And it feels awful.
+
Does she have a temperature?
Okay, forget it.
I'll be home in an hour.
Looks like I'm going to be missing
Puck told me about you two.
I'm going to tell Figgins and get you fired.
I'm ending it.
Not that there's
You shouldn't have come here with her.
I would have been fine.
What you did was wrong.
What you're doing with Puck is wrong.
You're so young... pretty...
Don't talk down to me.
It goes away, you know.
Not the pretty-- you'll always be pretty--
It happens really slow, and you don't even notice it,
I can't wait to feel different.
Don't wish away your life.
You're exactly where you're supposed to be.
I think I thought that being with an 18-year-old
(sighs)
All right.
I'm going to enjoy my last few hours of being a teacher.
I recommend that you enjoy being up on that stage.
ANNOUNCER:
Ladies and gentlemen, from McKinley High,
I am sorry, Quinn.
(Gloria Gaynor's
"I Will Survive" begins)
♪ At first I was afraid,
I was petrified ♪
♪ Kept thinking I could never live without you by my side ♪
♪ But then I spent so many nights ♪
♪ Thinking how you did me wrong ♪
♪ And I grew strong ♪
♪ And I learned how to get along ♪
♪ And so you're back ♪
♪ From outer space,
I just walked in ♪
♪ To find you here with that sad look upon your face ♪
♪ I should have changed the stupid lock ♪
♪ I should have made you leave your key ♪
♪ If I'd have known for just one second ♪
♪ You'd be back to bother me ♪
♪ Oh, now, go ♪
♪ Walk out the door ♪
♪ Just turn around now ♪
♪ 'Cause you're not welcome anymore... ♪
We got this.
Yeah, we do.
♪ You think I'd crumble ♪
♪ You think I'd lay down and die ♪
♪ I'm a survivor ♪
♪ What? ♪
♪ I'm not gonna give up ♪
♪ I'm not gonna stop ♪
♪ What? ♪
♪ I'm gonna work harder ♪
♪ I'm a survivor,
I'm gonna make it ♪
♪ What? What? ♪
♪ I will survive, keep on survivin' ♪
♪ Thought I couldn't breathe without you, I'm inhaling ♪
♪ You thought I couldn't see without you, perfect vision ♪
♪ You thought I couldn't last without you, but I'm lastin' ♪
♪ You thought that I would die without you, but I'm livin' ♪
♪ That I would fail without you, but I'm on top ♪
♪ Thought it would be over by now, but it won't stop ♪
♪ Thought that I would self-destruct ♪
♪ But I'm still here ♪
♪ Even in my years to come
I'm still gonna be here ♪
♪ I'm a survivor,
I'm not gonna give up ♪
♪ What? What? ♪
♪ I'm not gonna stop,
I'm gonna work harder ♪
♪ What? What? ♪
♪ I'm a survivor,
I'm gonna make it ♪
♪ What? What? ♪
♪ I will survive, keep on survivin' ♪
♪ Oh, no, not I,
I will survive ♪
♪ Oh, as long as I know how to love ♪
♪ I know I'll stay alive ♪
♪ I've got all my life to live ♪
♪ And I've got all my love to give ♪
♪ And I'll survive,
I will survive, hey, hey ♪
♪ I'm a survivor,
I'm not gonna give up ♪
♪ What? What? ♪
♪ I'm not gonna stop,
I'm gonna work harder ♪
♪ What? What? ♪
♪ I'm a survivor,
I'm gonna make it ♪
♪ What? What? ♪
♪ I will survive, keep on survivin' ♪
♪ I will survive. ♪
(cheering and applause)
+
ANNOUNCER:
Also from McKinley High,
(cheering and applause)
♪ A-boo, boo, boo, boo, boo ♪
♪ You went to school to learn, girl ♪
♪ Things you never, never knew before ♪
♪ Like "I" before "E" except after "C" ♪
♪ And why two plus two makes four ♪
♪ Now, now, now,
I'm gonna teach you ♪
♪ Teach you, teach you ♪
♪ All about love, dear ♪
♪ All about love ♪
♪ Sit yourself down and take a seat ♪
♪ All you gotta do is repeat after me ♪
♪ ABC, easy as one, two, three ♪
♪ Or simple as do re mi ♪
♪ ABC, one, two, three, baby, you and me, girl ♪
♪ ABC ♪
♪ Easy as one, two, three ♪
♪ Or simple as do re mi ♪
♪ ABC, one, two three ♪
♪ Baby, you and me, girl ♪
♪ Just a, a little bit ♪
♪ Come on, let me love you ♪
♪ Come on ♪
♪ Just a little bit ♪
♪ Little bit ♪
♪ Teach, teach, sing it out ♪
♪ Come on, come on ♪
♪ Come on, let me show you what it's all about ♪
♪ Reading, writing, arithmetic ♪
♪ Are the branches on the learning tree ♪
♪ Well, listen, without the roots of love ♪
♪ Let me tell you, girl ♪
♪ Your education ain't complete ♪
♪ T-t-t-teacher's gonna show you ♪
♪ Show you, show you ♪
♪ How to get an "A" ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na ♪
♪ Spell me, you, add the two ♪
♪ Listen to me, baby, that's all you gotta do ♪
♪ Oh, ABC, it's easy as one, two, three ♪
♪ Or simple as do re mi ♪
♪ ABC, one, two, three, baby, you and me, girl ♪
♪ ABC ♪
♪ It's easy ♪
♪ It's like counting up to three ♪
♪ Sing a simple melody ♪
♪ Do re mi, ABC ♪
♪ That's how easy love can be, sing a simple melody ♪
♪ One, two, three, you and me ♪
♪ Ah, yeah! ♪
Sit down, girl!
I think I love you!
No! Get up, girl!
Show me what you can do!
♪ Shake it, shake it, baby ♪
♪ Come on now ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh ♪
♪ One, two, three, baby ♪
♪ That's how easy love can be ♪
♪ ABC, it's easy ♪
♪ It's like counting up to three ♪
♪ One, two, three ♪
♪ Sing a simple melody ♪
♪ Do re mi, ABC ♪
♪ That's how easy love can be ♪
♪ I'm-a gonna teach you how to sing it out, sing it out ♪
♪ Sing it out, sing it out, sing it ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Baby, ABC, it's easy ♪
♪ It's like counting up to three ♪
♪ One, two, three ♪
♪ Sing a simple melody ♪
♪ Do re mi, ABC ♪
♪ That's how easy love can be ♪
♪ I'm-a gonna teach you how to sing it out, sing it out ♪
♪ Easy as one, two, three. ♪
(cheering and applause)
(Janet Jackson's
"Control" begins)
This is a story about control.
My control.
Control of what I say, control of what I do.
And this time,
I'm gonna do it my way.
(dance beat starts)
♪ When I was 17,
I did what people told me ♪
♪ Uh ♪
♪ I did what my father said and let my mother mold me ♪
♪ But that was long ago ♪
♪ I'm in ♪
♪ Control ♪
♪ And now I've got a lot ♪
♪ Ow! ♪
♪ Control ♪
♪ To get what I want ♪
♪ Never gonna stop ♪
♪ Control ♪
♪ And now I'm all grown up ♪
♪ Jam ♪
♪ Whoo, whoo ♪
♪ Rebel ♪
♪ That's right ♪
♪ Got my own mind ♪
♪ I want to make my own decisions ♪
♪ When it has to do with my life, my life ♪
♪ I want to be the one in control ♪
♪ So let me take you by the hand and lead you on this dance ♪
♪ 'Cause what I've got is because I took a chance ♪
♪ I don't want to rule the world ♪
♪ Just want to run my life ♪
♪ So make your life a little easier ♪
♪ When you get the chance, just take control ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh ♪
♪ Now I've got a lot ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Control ♪
♪ Now I'm all grown up ♪
♪ Ooh! ♪
♪ Free at last ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh, yeah ♪
♪ Free ♪
♪ Now control this ♪
♪ Uh ♪
♪ 'Cause I've got my own mind ♪
♪ Gonna make my own decisions ♪
♪ When it has to do with my life ♪
♪ I want to be the one in control ♪
♪ I'm in control ♪
♪ Uh ♪
♪ Ah ♪
♪ I'm in control ♪
♪ Uh ♪
♪ Ah. ♪
(cheering and applause)
♪ Ooh, ooh ♪
♪ Ah ♪
♪ I'm gonna make a change ♪
♪ For once in my life ♪
♪ It's gonna feel real good ♪
♪ Gonna make a difference ♪
♪ Gonna make it right ♪
♪ As I turn up the collar ♪
♪ On my favorite winter coat ♪
♪ This wind is blowin' my mind ♪
♪ I see the kids in the street ♪
♪ Without enough to eat ♪
♪ Who am I to be blind ♪
♪ Pretending not to see their needs? ♪
♪ A summer's disregard ♪
♪ A broken bottle top ♪
♪ And one man's soul ♪
♪ They follow each other on the wind, you know ♪
♪ 'Cause they got nowhere to go ♪
♪ That's why I want you to know ♪
♪ I'm starting with the man in the mirror ♪
♪ I'm asking him to change his ways ♪
♪ And no message could have been any clearer ♪
♪ If you wanna make the world a better place ♪
♪ Take a look at yourself and then make a change ♪
♪ I'm starting with the man in the mirror ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪ I'm asking him to change his ways ♪
♪ Change his ways ♪
♪ And no message could have been any clearer ♪
♪ If you wanna make the world a better place ♪
♪ Take a look at yourself and then make a change ♪
♪ You gotta get it right, while you got the time ♪
♪ 'Cause when you close your heart then you close your mind ♪
♪ I'm starting with the man in the mirror ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪ I'm asking him to change his ways ♪
♪ And no message could have been any clearer ♪
♪ If you wanna make the world a better place ♪
♪ Take a look at yourself and then make that change ♪
♪ Stand up ♪
♪ Make that change ♪
♪ Stand up and let yourself now ♪
♪ Man in the mirror ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ Make that change ♪
♪ Stand up, stand up in love ♪
♪ You know it, you know it, you know it, you know ♪
♪ Change... ♪
♪ Make that change. ♪
(cheering and applause)
+
(cheering, whooping)
Get over here!
Gave it our all.
Yeah, we did.
Top dogs! Yes!
This is what I was missing!
I just...
I can't believe it.
I can't believe he actually came.
He stood and...
Michael.
May I speak with you?
Both of you?
Dancing is your talent, your dream.
That's what you tried to tell me.
And that's what
I saw tonight.
This is your path, son, so you must follow it,
And your mother and I, we will
Apply to dance schools-- the best ones.
Dad...
Dad, I... I missed the deadlines, I think.
No, you didn't.
I sent in your applications, just in case.
I kind of had to forge your signature, though.
I love you so much.
(honks horn)
As an award-winning clown,
I'd like to say
Third place-- The Unitards!
(cheering)
Harmony...
Hi. I just wanted to tell you
And just think,
I'm only a sophomore
Next year's going to be a bloodbath.
In second place...
...we have the Trouble Tones!
In first place is New Directions!
(cheering)
♪ ♪
(light switches clanking, echoing through auditorium)
Well, my suspension is officially over.
It'll still be on my transcript, though.
I'm just hoping that
Good luck with that.
Are you going to go tell
Figgins about Shelby?
'Cause I just...
I still think
I came here to talk to you, actually.
To tell you I'm not going to tell.
Why?
Because I love Beth, and I don't want to ruin her life.
I wanted to thank you actually.
For what?
For keeping me from doing something stupid.
Something I would have regretted my entire life.
We're kind of friends, huh?
Kind of.
What do you think about Yale?
Oh, no, I have my sights set on NYADA.
No, for me.
I'm not the singer that you and Kurt are,
And I really do like to perform.
Yeah.
Certainly would nail all the parts where the girl has to cry.
No, I think it's a great idea.
I mean, especially since you won't have me to compete with.
You're a lot better than you know.
Well, I'll see you at Glee Club.
Where are you going?
I have a couple people
I need to talk to.
Okay, well, I don't know
Not with the Yale application,
We were better.
I don't know, I think it could have gone either way.
It was that damn Trouty Mouth.
Even I felt a little something in my lady loins
All right, ladies, girl talk.
No. Uh-uh. Don't you dare try and give us a pep talk.
Or ask us to come back to New
Directions-- not interested.
Wait, is it even possible?
Do you think they would
Of course they would take us back.
But I'm telling you,
I'm not going.
Do you know what growing up is about?
Losing things.
In six months, we'll all be gone, scattered.
We'll keep in touch.
Yeah, but it won't be the same.
When we see each other, it'll be a special occasion.
It'll be different.
I don't want to grow up yet.
I'm not ready to lose you girls.
What are we supposed to do?
Come back to Glee Club and sing background for Blaine and Berry
I'm not doing that again.
We know what it feels like to be out front now.
What if Mr. Shue agreed to let the Trouble Tones
Well, even if Mr. Shue did agree to that, Rachel never would.
What if I told you that they both already did?
I'm listening.
Look, I know I went a little crazy.
But I'm here now.
I'm 17-- I have the rest of my life in front of me.
I love Glee Club.
I love you girls.
And when we're 27, or 87,
I want us to be able to look back on these next couple months
Can't do that if we're not all together.
We're doing a big number in the auditorium
We could use a couple more girl voices.
Let me know if you hear about anybody who might want to join.
♪ Give me a second ♪
♪ I need to get my story straight ♪
♪ My friends are in the bathroom ♪
♪ Getting higher than the Empire State ♪
♪ My lover he's waiting for me just across the bar ♪
♪ My seat's been taken by some sunglasses ♪
♪ Asking 'bout a scar and ♪
♪ I know I gave it to you months ago ♪
♪ I know you're trying to forget ♪
♪ But between the drinks and subtle things ♪
♪ The holes in my apologies ♪
♪ You know I'm trying hard to take it back ♪
♪ So if by the time the bar closes ♪
♪ And you feel like falling down ♪
♪ I'll carry you home ♪
♪ Tonight ♪
♪ We are young ♪
♪ So let's set the world on fire ♪
♪ We can burn brighter than the sun ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ Tonight ♪
♪ We are young ♪
♪ So let's set the world on fire ♪
♪ Fire ♪
♪ We can burn brighter than the sun ♪
♪ Carry me home tonight ♪
♪ Just carry me home tonight ♪
♪ The angels never arrived ♪
♪ But I can hear the choir ♪
♪ So someone come and carry me home... ♪
♪ Tonight ♪
♪ We are young ♪
♪ So let's set the world on fire ♪
♪ We can burn brighter than the sun ♪
♪ We are young ♪
♪ La-la-la-la-la-la-la ♪
♪ So let's set the world on fire ♪
♪ We can burn brighter than the sun ♪
♪ So if by the time the bar closes ♪
♪ And you feel like falling down ♪
♪ I'll carry you home tonight. ♪
Synced By YesCool and Gortz www.MY-SUBS.com